{
    "subject": "resource/Movie4k.to",
    "predicate": "ontology/language",
    "object": "resource/German_language",
    "human_readable": "The language of Movie4k.to is German.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9618499279022217,
            "question": "Is Movie4k.to a German-language website?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9157217144966125,
            "question": "Is there a possibility that Movie4k.to offers content in other languages besides German?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8247766494750977,
            "question": "Would a German speaker find Movie4k.to intuitive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7726890444755554,
            "question": "If you don't speak German, would Movie4k.to be easy to use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6132339239120483,
            "question": "In what language would you find content on Movie4k.to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5881486535072327,
            "question": "What language is used on the website Movie4k.to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5731800198554993,
            "question": "What language setting would you expect to see on Movie4k.to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.447244256734848,
            "question": "What implications might the language of Movie4k.to have for its user base?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42465126514434814,
            "question": "Could the language barrier be a factor in Movie4k.to's popularity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3551301658153534,
            "question": "How common is it for websites like Movie4k.to to use a specific language?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of Movie4k.to is German.",
            "html": "dbpedia_489_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could the language barrier be a factor in Movie4k.to's popularity?",
            "html": "dbpedia_489_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What implications might the language of Movie4k.to have for its user base?",
            "html": "dbpedia_489_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language setting would you expect to see on Movie4k.to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_489_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_489_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_489_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_489_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_489_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_489_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_489_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_489_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_489_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_489_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_489_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation:\n\nThe documents mention Movie4k as a German album released in 2021, and also mention that Movie2k.to serves English and German-speaking areas. However, there is no specific information about the language of Movie4k.to.\n\nSo, the answer would be:\n\n{'output': 'no'}\n\nThis means that based on the given context, it's not possible to confirm whether the language of Movie4k.to is indeed German."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents indicate that Movie4k.to, which was previously known as Movie2k.to and serves primarily English and German-speaking areas. Therefore, the statement \"The language of Movie4k.to is German\" can be considered correct based on the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information suggests that Movie4K is a German album, but the fact provided about Movie4k.to being a pirate movie site does not specify the language of its content.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}